Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative records, 1982-2008; Accession 2010-A-064
  - Assessment Group – Ref Serv Stat, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Memo – Study of Library Serv - (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Memo – Study of Library Serv, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Assessment Reader Survey, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Assessment - Reader survey, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Assessment - Reader, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Reader Survey Report, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Assessment – Research Servi & Col, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Assessment – Research Serv & Col, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Assessment – Science Grad, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Assessment – Scully, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Assessment: SERVQUAL Phase II, Spr 1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Assessment – Shoah Fd. Project, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - DLF Assessment on Use/Usability, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Assessment – SSL User Surveys, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Assessment – Wireless, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - AUL Presentation – Knowledge Mgmt, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Brodkin Collection, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Contingency Service Plan, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Film Study Center, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - GIS, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Info Kiosk, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Institute for Learning Innovation, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Joint Geospatial Steering Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Library Annual Report, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Loan – Franklin Bust – Phil Mus of Art, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Library Policy Manual, 1982-1993 (Box 1, Folder 37-39)
  - Library Policy, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Library Policy, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Library Policy, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Library Policy, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Library Policy, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Library Policy, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Library Policy, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Collection Space Management
    - Project Management, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - ELI Express, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Collection Space Management, 2004
    - Orbis record, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Operations, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Stack Management, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Collection Space Management - 2006
    - Steering Committee (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Collection ID Selection (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Collection Space Management, 2004
    - Summer '04 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - CCL (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Mudd (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Public Relations (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Collection Space Management
    - Budget - 2005 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - AOB (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Space Pilot for Knowledge Management - 2004 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Space Planning for Collection – 2002 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - SQIC Retreat - 2000 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Specs for Rudolph Building – 2007 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Davis Grant Final, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Eli Imaging America, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Patron correspondence, 1996-2009; Accession 2014-A-050
  Restricted until January 1, 2044
  - A-C, 1996-2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General
    Includes anonymous correspondence
  - D-G, 1996-2009 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - H-L, 1997-2008 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - M-P, 1997-2008 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - R-T, 1997-2009 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - U-Z, 1997-2003 (Box 2, Folder 6)